<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gluckstein</string>
    <string name="car_accidents">Car Accidents</string>
    <string name="medical_malpractice">Medical Malpractice</string>
    <string name="birth_injury">Birth Injury</string>
    <string name="wrongful_death">Wrongful Death</string>
    <string name="brain_injury">Brain Injury</string>
    <string name="spinal_injury">Spinal Injury</string>
    <string name="long_term_disability">Long Term Disability</string>
    <string name="slip_and_falls">Slip and Falls</string>
    <string name="product_liability">Product Liability</string>
    <string name="class_actionMass_tort">Class Action/Mass Tort</string>

    <string name="car_accident_Text">
        <b><big><font fgcolor="#212A53">WHAT TO DO AFTER A MOTOR VEHICLE ACCIDENT</font></big></b> \n \t When you or a loved one suffers from a serious injury caused by a motor vehicle accident, the aftermath can be life-changing and overwhelming. You may be faced with a lengthy recovery, daily pain and suffering, a complex insurance claim, an inability to work or to care for your family, among other unexpected challenges.
        \n\n At Gluckstein Lawyers, our personal injury lawyers and their teams are committed to your well-being. If you require support because you have sustained an injury from a motor vehicle accident, we are here for you. No question is too small. Contact us today to speak with a personal injury lawyer. We are here to listen.
   \n\n <b><big>Should I Get a Lawyer for a Car Accident?</big></b>
    \n Gluckstein Personal Injury Lawyers is here to help when you need it most, so you are never alone. Our skilled team will guide you through the complex legalities of a claim. Our in-house medical consultant can help you understand your injuries and connect you or your loved ones with valuable resources. You can contact us for a no-obligation, free consultation. Our personal injury lawyers do not charge any legal fees until your case is settled.
    \n \n <b><big>Full Legal Services for Car Accident Claims</big></b>
        \nAt Gluckstein Lawyers, we aim to simplify the legal process, so that you can focus on getting better. We will walk you through the various legal resources available and explain how they might relate to your case.
       \n \n The different types of motor vehicle accident claims include:
        \n<li>Car accidents</li>
        \n<li> accidents</li>
        \n<li>Motorcycle accidents</li>
        \n<li>nBicycle and pedestrian accidents</li>
        \n<li>Hit-and-Run accidents</li>
        \n<li>Drunk driving accidents, and resulting bar or tavern liability</li>
        \n
        \n <b><big>How to Make An Insurance Claim</big></b>
        \n Every car accident case varies, so be sure to speak with a car accident lawyer to discuss the details of your situation. Our car accident lawyers in Toronto, Ottawa, and Niagara serve personal injury victims and their families across Ontario.
        \n\n
        If you have sustained an injury from a car accident, there are two ways to claim compensation:
        \n
        \n<li>You may be entitled to receive accident benefits, also called no-fault benefits, from your insurance company, regardless of who is at fault for the car accident.</li>
        \n<li>You may be entitled to receive an award of damages if another person is at fault or if you are only partly at fault for the car accident. This is called a Tort Claim and is commenced by way of a formal lawsuit.</li>
        \n
        \n <b><big>No-Fault Accident Benefits Claim</big></b>
        \n When involved in a motor vehicle collision in Ontario, you can claim benefits from your own insurance company, regardless of who was at fault. This is normally the first course of action following a car accident. Depending on the specific policy in question, the benefits claimed can include:
        \n<li>Medical and Rehabilitation Benefits</li>
        \n<li>Attendant Care Benefits</li>
        \n<li>Income Replacement Benefits</li>
        \n<li>Non-Earner Benefits</li>
        \n<li>Caregiver Benefits</li>
        \n<li>Housekeeping Benefits</li>
        \n<li>Death and Funeral Benefits</li>
        \n<li>Other Benefits</li>
        \n\n
        <b>You must notify your insurance company within 7 days, or as soon reasonably possible, that you wish to apply for no-fault accident benefits. You must file a completed Application Form with your insurance company within 30 days after receiving it.</b>
        \n\n
        <b><big>The Tort Claim</big></b>
        \n If you are a driver and another person is at fault or partially at fault, a passenger, cyclist, or pedestrian injured in a car accident in Ontario, you can pursue legal action against the person or persons responsible for negligence. Under personal injury law, a tort claim allows you to gain compensation for damages that were caused by another party’s negligence. A lawsuit against an at-fault party must be issued by way of Statement of Claim with the court within two years of the date of the incident.
        \n\n
        <b><big>What Can I Sue For?</big></b>
        \n There are various categories of damages that an injured party can seek compensation for by way of a lawsuit, including:
        \n<li>Pain, suffering, loss of enjoyment of life</li>
        \n<li>Income-related losses</li>
        \n<li>Health care expenses</li>
        \n<li>Family Law Act damages</li>
        \n<li>Housekeeping and home maintenance expenses</li>
        \n<li>Other quantified losses</li>
        \n
        \n
        <b><big>What is a Threshold?</big></b>
        \n To make a tort claim, you must prove that your injury meets the “threshold” as defined by the Insurance Act. The threshold is a description of the severity of your injury. To meet the threshold, your injury must result in a:
        \n<li>permanent serious impairment of an important physical, mental or psychological function; or</li>
        \n<li>permanent serious disfigurement</li>
        \n\n
        <b><big>What if my injury meets the threshold?</big></b>
        \nIf your injury meets the threshold you may be entitled to recover damages from a motor vehicle accident for pain, suffering and loss of enjoyment of life, health care expenses, family law act damages, and other quantified losses. At Gluckstein Lawyers, we are here to help you understand what damages you can recover. It is important to speak to one of our personal injury lawyers to help you understand your rights.
        \n\n
        <b>Remember</b>: if you were injured by an uninsured or unknown party,<b>you should still seek out legal counsel</b>. It is advised to consult a personal injury lawyer for a tort claim for a motor vehicle accident.
        \n\n
        <b><big>Insurance Companies</big></b>
        \n Accident victims are not always treated fairly by their insurance company. They may attempt to confuse you with legal jargon and make it seem as if you do not have a claim at all when, in reality, you may. Offering you a one-time large sum as compensation is another trick insurance companies might use. Our experienced car accident lawyers will work to advise you on the best course of action in your situation.  It is essential to factor in pain and suffering and future needs for your injuries, which often means that a one-time lump-sum settlement might not be sufficient.
        \n\n
        It is highly recommended that you do not provide a statement about your injuries to the insurance company, whether you feel fine or are in pain, without consulting with a personal injury lawyer. They will use it as evidence against you later on when you file a claim. Being in a car accident may have been so traumatic for you that you want to speak with your family and friends about it and possibly talk about it on social media. While you should talk with a professional to deal with the trauma, whatever you say or post online may also be used later on when you file a claim or are in court because of the incident.
        \n\n
        For this reason, it is a good idea to keep a diary of how you feel on a day-to-day basis and record instances in which your injuries affected your normal activities, such as bending and walking. If the court case is extended to a year or more after the car accident, the diary can be used to help you fill in the gaps of your memory. Moreover, keep anything you were prescribed for your injuries, such as prescriptions, crutches, and casts, or any relevant photographs. These elements are classified as objective evidence, and they are highly valued in car accident cases.
        \n\n
        Dealing with insurance companies is one of Gluckstein Personal Injury Lawyers’ specialties, so make sure that you contact us for a free consultation when you encounter difficulties with your insurance company.
        \n\n
        <b><big>Settling Your Claim</big></b>
        \nAcross Ontario, a tort claim can only be settled once you have a full understanding of your personal injuries and how they will impact your future. This means seeking help from a medical professional. With a complete understanding of your current and future medical needs, an appropriate settlement can be reached.
        \n\n
        Working with a car accident lawyer will also reduce the amount of time the case takes since they know how best to approach your situation. They can help you navigate through the different stages of a lawsuit and may advise you as to when it might be beneficial to settle out of court, before going to a trial, through arbitration, mediation or negotiation.
        \n\n
        If you’re wondering, “When do I need a lawyer for a car accident?”, it’s best to find one right away! It is best to be proactive so that you have sufficient time to file the proper paperwork and to begin your recovery process. To learn more about how we can help you, or to discuss a potential claim, contact us at Gluckstein Lawyers.



    </string>

    <string name="medical_malpractice_Text">
        If you believe you have been injured by medical malpractice, our personal injury team at Gluckstein Lawyers can help you.  We have a team of medical malpractice lawyers in Toronto, Ottawa, and Niagara dedicated to pursuing cases across Ontario on behalf of patients injured through medical negligence.
        Doctors, nurses, midwives, hospitals and other health care providers are expected to provide you with medical care that meets certain standards.  When the care you receive fails to meet those standards, injury can occur and responsibility for that injury may fall on the health care provider.
        In a medical malpractice case, our team seeks to recover compensation for the losses that you have suffered due to substandard medical care.  No matter where in Ontario you live, we are available to help you with a medical malpractice claim.  We pursue cases involving birth trauma, brain injury, spinal cord injury, or any other adverse medical outcome that leads to significant disability or financial losses.
        \n\n
        <b><big>Pursuing Your Medical Malpractice Claim</big></b>
        \n
        \n
        Claims for damages arising out of medical malpractice are complex and challenging.  It is essential, therefore, that you be represented by medical malpractice lawyers with experience and a proven track record.  Where you pursue a medical negligence claim, your lawyer must help you prove that the health care providers failed to meet the standards of care and that the failure to do so resulted in harm.  Proving these claims involves close and detailed work between your lawyer and independent medical experts that your lawyer hires to advise and assist you with your case.
        \n\n
        In many circumstances, medical malpractice cases need to be started quickly.  There is a two-year limitation period for suing a medical practitioner or hospital.  That limitation period begins to run from the date you knew or ought to have known of facts giving rise to a claim.  For medical negligence that results in death, the two-year limitation period runs from the date of death.  For people under disability[1] and children under 18 years of age, the limitation period may be longer.
        \n\n
        In most cases, however, it is prudent to pursue your case as soon as you suspect that you have suffered a bad outcome as a result of medical malpractice.  It is usually helpful to begin these cases while things are still fresh in your mind.  As well, your personal injury lawyer needs to collect all of the relevant medical records in a timely way to identify the issues in your case and to ensure that your medical experts are asked the right questions.  If you wait too long, it may be too late.
        \n\n
        Medical malpractice cases are expensive to pursue.  Where we believe your claim has merit, we will agree to prosecute your claim based on a contingency fee agreement.  That means that we don’t get paid unless you get paid.
        \n\n
        <b><big>Experienced Representation for Personal Injury Claims</big></b>
        \n\n
        Experienced medical malpractice counsel, like our team at Gluckstein Lawyers, know how to prove fault on the part of the medical practitioners and know how to develop your case for damages.  We are meticulous in advocating for your interests and those of your family members.  Our medical malpractice team is led by a lawyer with over 30 years of experience in medical malpractice cases.
        \n\n
        The medical malpractice claims we handle include:
        \n\n
        \n<li>Birth trauma</li>
        \n<li>Administration errors</li>
        \n<li>Surgical errors</li>
        \n<li>Nursing errors</li>
        \n<li>Chiropractic errors</li>
        \n<li>Misdiagnosis and delayed diagnosis</li>
        \n<li>Lack of informed consent</li>
        \n<li>Midwife negligence</li>
        \n\n
        <b><big>Your Medical Malpractice Case Is in Good Hands</big></b>
        \n\n
        Gluckstein Lawyers believe in making a connection with our clients, so that you feel at ease knowing you have the support you need under difficult circumstances. Since 1962, our firm has represented thousands of injured people, advocating for their interests, assisting with access to needed therapies, and obtaining the compensation they deserve.
        \n\n
        Your first consultation is free.  Please contact use at info@gluckstein.com and arrange your free consultation with a member of our medical malpractice team.

        </string>
    <string name="birth_injury_Text">
        Having a baby is an exciting time, an event that should be filled with great joy.  Every expectant parent has dreams of a life full of accomplishment and happiness for their child.  While most children are born healthy, a small number of newborns suffer injury at or near the time of birth. These traumatic birth events are devastating for every parent.  Once the initial shock has started to wear off, most parents want to know what happened to their baby. Questions arise about why their baby was injured, and whether the injury could have and should have been prevented.  This is the time to turn to a Birth Injury Lawyer for help.  Finding the answers to these questions can be difficult.  An experienced Birth Injury Lawyer can help answer these questions for parents.  As lawyers with considerable experience in Birth Injury cases, we are here to help.  If you have any questions about Birth Injuries, we may be able to help you find the answers.
        \n\n
        <b><big>What Are Birth Injuries?</big></b>
        \n\n
        Most Birth Injuries are related to a disruption in blood flow to the baby’s brain, although other forms of trauma also occur at or around the time of birth.  Injury to the baby’s brain from impaired blood flow to the brain can occur before labour, during labour and delivery, or shortly after birth.  If severe enough, the impaired flow of oxygen can cause permanent injury to the baby’s brain, resulting in a diagnosis of cerebral palsy.  Unfortunately, Cerebral Palsy is a permanent injury to the brain that often results in severe motor dysfunction, cognitive impairment and developmental delays.  It can also affect vision and hearing and can often cause seizures. Cerebral Palsy resulting from birth trauma will have a dramatic impact on many aspects of their lives.  They will have need for care, therapies and surgical interventions, often for life.
        \n\n
        Other injuries from physical trauma can also occur, most notably from shoulder dystocia, resulting in injury to the nerves in the neck, shoulder and arm.  Other forms of Birth Trauma are described below.
        \n\n
        <b><big>Types of Birth Injuries</big></b>
        \n\n
        Some examples of birth injuries would include:
        \n
        \n<li>Cerebral Palsy</li>
        \n<li>Brachial Plexus Injuries</li>
        \n<li>Erb’s Palsy</li>
        \n<li>Fetal and Neonatal Stroke</li>
        \n<li>Hypoglycemia leading to brain injury</li>
        \n<li>Hypoxic Ischemic Encephalopathy (HIE)</li>
        \n<li>Kernicterus (brain injury) from Hyperbilirubinemia</li>
        \n<li>Meconium Aspiration Syndrome</li>
        \n<li>Negligent Resuscitation of a Newborn</li>
        \n<li>Newborn Infections</li>
        \n<li>Periventricular Leukomalacia (PVL)</li>
        \n<li>Seizures</li>
        \n<li>Trauma from Forceps and Vacuum</li>
        \n\n
        <b><big>What Our Birth Trauma Lawyers Can Do</big></b>
        \n\n
        If you think your child or grandchild has suffered a Birth Injury that might have been preventable, we can help make that determination.  We start by meeting with you to get the facts.  We then obtain all the relevant medical records and perform a detailed and comprehensive review.  Where indicated, we will consult with highly qualified, respected and independent doctors to get the answers you need and deserve.
        \n\n
        <b><big>Consultation</big></b>
        \n\n
        There is no fee charged for your initial consultation about your Birth Trauma case.  In our first meeting, we will carefully discuss the relevant obstetrical history as well as the circumstances surrounding labour and delivery.  We will obtain the antenatal records, the labour and delivery records, the fetal heart tracings and the newborn records, at no cost to you.  Following our careful analysis of those records, we will again meet with you to discuss our findings and move your case in the right direction, again at no cost to you.
        \n\n
        <b><big>Investigation</big></b>
        \n\n
        If concerns are identified, following our review of your Birth Trauma case and our meeting with you to discuss the records and issues, we will consult with highly trained medical experts.  We seek support from these medical experts to demonstrate that the care provided did not lead up to reasonable expectations – called a breach of the standard of care.  We also seek medical support to prove that the failure to provide proper care resulted in your child’s Birth Injury – called “causation”.  Once we have the required expert support to establish your case, we can proceed with a claim for compensation for your child and your family.
        \n\n
        <b><big>Building the Case</big></b>
        \n\n
        The goal of a Birth Trauma medical malpractice claim is to get your child and your family the justice and compensation you deserve for an injury that should have been avoided.  The economic and emotional burden of caring for a child injured by Birth Trauma is enormous.  All affected families are in need of substantial assistance.  Your Birth Trauma Lawyer must ensure all the required steps are taken to get the compensation you deserve.  These cases are complex and usually take many years to prosecute.  Due to the complexity of these cases, it is important that you select a Birth Trauma lawyer with both experience and credentials
        \n\n
        <b><big>Contact a Birth Injury Lawyer Today</big></b>
        \n\n
        If you and your family have been affected by Birth Trauma, Gluckstein Lawyers can help you.  We have a team which includes lawyers, clerks and a client liaison who herself has experienced the entire process of a birth trauma case. Our birth injury lawyers in Toronto, Ottawa, and Niagara, Ontario have vast experience in these cases and will tirelessly advocate for your child and your family.

    </string>

    <string name="wrongful_death_Text">

        Every year in Ontario, hundreds of families lose a loved one resulting from fatal accidents. The law cannot bring a loved one back, but a legal claim can bring a sense of closure and help with financial strains following the accident.
        \n\n
        Moving forward after losing a loved one is incredibly difficult. We provide compassionate support and guidance as we advocate on your behalf during this difficult time. Our wrongful death lawyers in Toronto, Ottawa, and Niagara, Ontario understand the difficulty of discussing the unexpected passing of a loved one and are here to support you and your family.

    </string>
    <string name="brain_injury_Text">

        Experiencing a traumatic brain injury is frightening and generally happens after a blow to the head or another unexpected injury causes damage to the brain. Unfortunately, the symptoms do not always show up immediately. At times, they surface a couple of days or weeks following the injury – which can come as a surprise to the victim. This delayed onset can be very confusing and disorienting. It may be difficult to determine the cause of the brain injury.
        \n\n
        There will be those who try to connect your brain injury to something completely unrelated to the trauma you experienced earlier. It may take a brain injury lawyer to help you retrace your steps and gather proof of the cause.
        \n\n
        At Gluckstein Lawyers, we are known as brain injury lawyers in Toronto who can focus on the cause of the injury, identify the negligent party, and pursue the maximum compensation you might receive. Brain injury cases are legally complex, with frequent obstacles and challenges that must be navigated before anything can be resolved. Our brain injury lawyers in Toronto, Ottawa, and Niagara, Ontario will get involved early on in order to get to the bottom of your particular situation and pave the way for maximum results The success of your brain injury claim is what drives our mission at Gluckstein Lawyers.

    </string>
    <string name="spinal_injury_Text">

        Spinal cord injuries are highly traumatic and often critical. They frequently arise from a sudden fall or blow to the head or torso, and can be life-threatening. This type of injury can lead to permanent damage, such as a complete loss of function below the actual level of the trauma. Fortunately, there are rehabilitation services and devices that can help the patient lead as much of a normal life as possible. There are also therapies that can assist in stabilizing the spine and surrounding structures. Unfortunately, specialized treatment and devices for spinal cord injuries are costly and can be well beyond the means of victims and their loved ones.
        \n\n
        Our spinal injury lawyers in Toronto, Ottawa, and Niagara, Ontario who make it their business to help clients receive the financial support they deserve and need. Indeed, Gluckstein Lawyers are committed to helping those who face a life of rehabilitation from a spinal cord injury. Our commitment also extends outward – we are extensively involved with not-for-profit organizations that support people with spinal cord injuries.
        \n\n
        On the legal front, spinal cord injury claims require representation by lawyers who understand and can handle the complexities of these cases. An experienced spinal injury lawyer can focus on identifying the negligent parties, the cause of the injury, and the anticipated long-term impact for the individual and his or her family. Our mission at Gluckstein Lawyers is to determine the best way for our clients to receive the most favourable result possible, so they can look ahead to a future life of dignity and financial security.

    </string>
    <string name="long_term_disability_Text">

        Our long-term disability lawyers will work with you to get the right compensation and support for the physical, emotional, and mental trauma caused by an accident, injury or illness.
        \n\n
        You may have purchased your LTD policy privately, or you may have coverage through a package of group benefits made available to you by your employer. Or, your claim may arise under a mortgage disability policy that your bank required you to purchase when you financed your home or business. Your disability may be the result of Chronic Fatigue Syndrome (CFS), Myalgic Encephalomyelitis (ME), or Fibromyalgia (FM), or it may arise from a Cardiac, Respiratory, Immunologic, Neurologic, Mental Health, or other disabling conditions.
        \n\n
        Regardless of the cause of your disability or type of LTD coverage you have – private, group or mortgage disability – you may be legally entitled to continue receiving LTD benefits even though your insurer has told you differently.
        \n\n
        Long-Term Disability policies exist to protect individuals who are unable to work due to a disability or illness by providing an income replacement benefit. If you are unable to work due to illness, accident, or injury for an extended period, you may qualify for long-term disability benefits through your insurer. A personal injury lawyer can help you access these benefits if your claims are being denied or if your benefits are cut off while you are still disabled or recovering.
        \n\n
        Each Long-Term Disability policy is different. To qualify for Long-Term Disability benefits, you will have to meet the eligibility criteria as outlined in your policy. This will include meeting the definition of “disability” that is described in your policy.
        \n\n
        <b>Long-Term Disability Benefits</b>
        \nWhen you’ve filed your disability claim, your insurance company may give you the green light to receive your benefits. However, it is important to know that some insurance companies may terminate your benefits, stating that you now fall under a change in definition.
        \n
        This term indicates that your situation has changed since you started receiving benefits. A two-year period is the general cut-off mark, signalling your switch from being unable to work “in his or her own occupation” to “any occupation.” The moment your benefits stop, you need to call our disability lawyers in Toronto, Ottawa, or Niagara, Ontario. It is not up to your insurance company to decide when your benefits end.
        \n
        On the other hand, insurance companies can immediately reject your disability claim in certain circumstances. There are many injuries or illnesses that they still do not acknowledge as valid reasons for benefits, which can explain your claim’s denial. This is another instance when our disability lawyers are well-suited to step in. We have represented many people throughout Ontario who have struggled with their insurance companies.
        \n\n
        <b>Objective Evidence</b>
        \n When clients experience physical disabilities, it’s easier to see them. They will wear a cast, have markings on their skin, or walk with a cane. Medication, casts, photos, and walking aids are objective evidence of the disability.
        \n
        When a disability is not evident, such as mental health and chronic pain, it’s harder to prove that an individual is suffering or incapable of working. Gluckstein’s disability lawyers are strategic in our approach and compassionate. We will explain your insurance policy and assist with any discrepancies and injustices, so you receive the compensation to which you are entitled.
        \n\n
        <b>Appeals</b>
        \n An insurance policy should be something you can rely on, although it is not always the case. If you or a family member is unable to work due for an extended period due to an accident, illness, or injury, we recommend that you consult with a disability personal injury lawyer as soon as possible. A lawyer can help determine if you have a potential claim against your insurer and can advise you on how best to appeal if your claim is denied.
        \n
        At Gluckstein Personal Injury Lawyers, we will consider all available remedies and decide upon the most appropriate course of action once we are retained and have sufficient information and evidence necessary to assess your disability claim.
        \n
        Gluckstein Lawyers offers free consultations and can help you navigate through the complex area of Long-Term Disability law.

    </string>
    <string name="slip_and_falls_Text">

        When you have been hurt badly on someone else’s property, whether that property is commercial, residential, or on public roads and sidewalks, you may not be at fault for your injuries. It is often the responsibility of the property owner to ensure the safety of their premises.
        \n\n
        Gluckstein personal injury lawyers have a decade’s worth of experience as legal advocates in Toronto, Ottawa, Niagara, and across Ontario. If you’ve been hurt in an accident, let us represent you and your family.
        \n\n
        <b><big>OCCUPIERS’ LIABILITY ACT</big></b>
        \nAccording to the Occupiers’ Liability Act, Ontario property owners have a duty to keep their properties safe and prevent slip-and-fall accidents.
        \n\n
        Examples of occupiers’ liability claims:
        \n\n
        \n<li>Slip-and-falls on icy sidewalks or private property, such as parking lots</li>
        \n<li>Trips on broken stairs or poorly lit staircases</li>
        \n<li>Hazardous materials left in highly trafficked areas</li>
        \n<li>Falling objects</li>
        \n<li>Store displays in dangerous areas</li>
        \n<li>Spills or debris on store floors</li>
        \n\n
        Slips, trips, and fall injuries can also be caused by seasonal negligence. Ice and rain can damage concrete over time, creating cracks and uneven terrain. If the company you hired to lay down salt during the winter doesn’t show up, occupants and visitors have a higher risk of being injured.
        \n\n
        It’s essential that property owners hire reliable and trust-worthy companies. Personal injuries, such as slip-and-fall accidents, can result as an example from cleaning crews who do not put up appropriate signage that warns passersby of recently waxed floors, for example.
        \n\n
        Buildings must be properly designed to meet codes and safety regulations. Solid stairs and handrails, as well as functioning escalators and elevators provide occupants and visitors with a basic method for travelling within the building.
        \n\n
        The Occupiers’ Liability Act applies to various types of individuals, including:
        \n\n
        \n<li>Landlords</li>
        \n<li>Store owners</li>
        \n<li>Hotel owners/property managers</li>
        \n<li>Restaurant owners</li>
        \n<li>Private homeowners</li>
        \n\n
        Every day, people are hurt as a result of preventable slip and fall-related incidents. Our firm’s lawyers take immediate action to investigate your injury and its cause, so you can receive the compensation you deserve. Gluckstein Lawyers provide a free initial consultation, so get in touch with us right away!
        \n\n
        It is important to keep in mind that there are some slip-and-fall exceptions in the Act, such as injuries that result from criminal activity like trespassing.
        \n\n
        <b><big>WORKING FOR ONTARIO FAMILIES</big></b>
        \n Children are highly active and aren’t always as careful as they should be because they are still learning about the world and their personal limits. This is why property owners have a responsibility to ensure that their property is child-friendly.
        \n\n
        Our firm’s slip-and-fall lawyers help families whose children have been seriously injured at locations such as camps, amusement parks, swimming pools, and other recreational facilities.
        \n\n
        \n <b><big>Consequences of a Slip-and-Fall Accident</big></b>
        \nSlip-and-falls can be a source of major damage to your body and may result in needing to take  time off from work or school. A personal injury can require many medical appointments and rehabilitation sessions. Families shouldn’t have to use their limited funds to deal with the repercussions of a preventable personal injury. Our team will help you file a claim to ensure you receive compensation and—depending on your case—long-term disability benefits.
        \n\n
        <b><big>FILE YOUR CLAIM WITH OUR PERSONAL INJURY LAWYERS</big></b>
        \nGluckstein Lawyers assess slip-and-fall claims, consult with medical specialists, and gather evidence to support your case. Whether you have experienced a slip-and-fall accident at work or at the park, we are dedicated to helping our community stay strong and on its feet.

    </string>
    <string name="product_liability_Text">
        At Gluckstein Lawyers, we provide advocacy that makes a difference. Helping you and your family is our first priority.
        \n\n
        You have the right to assume the product is safe when you purchase a product. When you take the initiative to launch a product liability claim, not only will you be able to assist your family, but you may also be preventing injury to someone else.
        \n\n
        We have been taking legal action on behalf of seriously injured individuals for more than five decades. Our team of product liability lawyers ion Toronto, Ottawa, and Niagara serve clients across Ontario. Contact Gluckstein Lawyers for a free initial consultation today.
        \n\n
        Among the product liability cases we pursue are:
        \n\n
        \n<li>Dangerous or toxic foodstuffs</li>
        \n<li>Unsafe toys</li>
        \n<li>Unsafe children’s products</li>
        \n<li>Unsafe household appliances</li>
        \n<li>Defective autos, airbags and car parts</li>
        \n<li>Defective safety equipment</li>
        \n<li>Toxic or unsafe house-building materials</li>
        \n<li>Defective machinery</li>
        \n<li>Defective recreational vehicles</li>
    </string>


    <string name="class_actionMass_tort_Text">
        <b><big>What is a Class Action Lawsuit?</big></b>
        \nA class action is a type of civil claim brought by one or more individuals on behalf of a larger group, made up of class members. Class Action lawsuits are common where the same party injures a group of people in the same way. The interests of the group are represented by one individual known as the “class representative.” The class is treated as a group that was injured, rather than a group of individuals that were injured. Rather than having each person bring his or her own lawsuit, a Class Action allows the group to collectively sue the at-fault party to resolve the claims in a single legal proceeding. Class Action lawsuits provide an efficient way to litigate common issues. They can focus on multiple areas of law, including personal injury and product liability.
        \n\n
        By creating a group or class, class action lawsuits create power in numbers. A Class Action is a way to equalize the playing field against a large entity, and Gluckstein Lawyers is committed to advocating on your behalf.
        \n\n
        <b><big>How Gluckstein Lawyers Can Help</big></b>
        \nClass Action lawsuits are lengthy and complicated. The legal battle will likely be difficult and protracted. The most important objective of a class action is to help individuals pursue legal action against large entities, such as corporations or governments that have deep pockets and access to resources. By joining a class action, individuals are provided with an opportunity to seek a legal remedy for the alleged damages. The appeal for members who join a class proceeding may owe to the overwhelming importance of the issues in dispute.
        \n\n
        There is nothing you have to do directly to join a class action. A court order defines the class action, and if you fall within the definition which is set by the court, you are automatically included, unless you decide you do not wish to participate in the suit. If you would like to preserve your right to pursue an individual case, you must opt-out of the class action. There will be a limited window of time for you to opt-out, which will be indicated in the certification order, which is sent out after the proceeding is certified. However, be aware that once you have opted out, you are no longer entitled to any settlement, which may be given if the case is resolved.
        \n\n
        <b><big>What is a Mass Tort Action</big></b>
        \nUnlike class-action lawsuits, a Mass Tort action involves many injured parties against one or a few at-fault parties. Mass Tort actions are similar to Class Actions; however, a Mass Tort action treats each injured party individually, rather than as an injured group. It can be an efficient and cost-effective way to navigate the legal system for multiple parties experiencing the same or similar injuries. A Mass Tort action provides an efficient way to litigate common issues. A Mass Tort action can focus in various areas of law, including personal injury, product liability and medical negligence.
        \n\n
        <b><big>Our Commitment to You</big></b>
        \nThe significance of the outcome of a class action litigation and mass tort lawsuit is meaningful not only for the plaintiffs but also for society at large. The impact of these types of lawsuits extends far beyond the legal remedy for the plaintiff and can correct or modify damaging behaviour or widely accepted practices. Our ability to advocate for clients  in class actions and mass tort lawsuits represents for us  a distinct and honourable professional achievement and is in keeping with our firm’s commitment to providing full-circle care to all our clients.
        \n\n
        <b><big>Trusted Expertise</big></b>
        \nGluckstein Lawyers is an experienced class action law firm. Currently, we are representing plaintiffs in a lawsuit against Repromed Fertility and the Ukrainian Airline Flight 752 plane crash. For almost 60 years, we’ve helped clients and their families move forward with dignity and trusted expertise when faced with life-altering injuries. Our team of class action lawyers in Toronto, Ottawa, and Niagara is committed to serving our clients throughout Ontario who depend on us during the most challenging times of their lives, and we are with them every step of the way.

    </string>
</resources>